land-of-web.com 2014-06-18

# Privacy Policy

Land-of-web.com (“website” or “site” or “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This document tells you about our online collection and use of data. By using this site, you understand and agree to the terms of this privacy policy.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

We use web stat services to track the location, browser, operating system and screen resolution of our visitors i.e. information that the visitor sends via their browser. We use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit. We use this data only to operate and improve our website. We do not collect private information about each individual.

Email addresses and names are only provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications.

We can use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send emails, any marketing communications materials, newsletters etc to inform you of new services, products or other information. 

We do not share your personal information with any outside parties.

**Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partner is Google Adsense, so take a look on its privacy policy.

The third-party ad servers or ad networks may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this document and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site.

We won`t be responsible for any errors or omissions contained within any 3rd party advertisement. You access any third-party websites at your own risk.

We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

**Publishing Policy**

In order to generate extra income to our website we may choose to use affiliate links and/or sponsored posts.

We do not participate in any kind of partner-linking system.

We respect the rights of authors, designers and developer that is why we always provide a backlinks to respective owners.

**Copyright**

Content may not be reproduced, distributed, translated, displayed, posted, communicated or used in any way without the received permission from the land-of-web.com.

**Contact Information**

if you have any concerns, questions or require any more information about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at birchnataly@gmail.com.
